Maltese, Serphin R.; Papers apap382
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Pre-Senate Files, 1935-1988; 1; 3.5 cubic ft.
  - Event Invitations, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Marchi, John - Press and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Maspeth/Long Island Expressway, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Ridgewood Post No. 123, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Crime Victims Advocacy, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bork, Robert - Supreme Court Nomination, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - The Bush Report, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Christ the King, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Clippings, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Health Systems Agency Budget Cuts, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - New York State Common Cause Study, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Regan, Edward - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Republican Volunteers, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Stuyvesant High School "Alumni Spectator", 1987 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Catholic War Veterans, 1987; Undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Death Penalty Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Juniper Park Civic Association Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Americas of Italian Heritage, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Christ the King, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Clippings, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Congressional Campaign: Announcement Speech, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Congressional Campaign: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Congressional Campaign: Designating Petitions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Congressional Campaign: Election Press, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Congressional Campaign: Endorsements and Contributions, 1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Congressional Campaign: Flyers and Mailers, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Congressional Campaign: General, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Congressional Campaign: News Releases, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Congressional Campaign: "Serf's Grand Opening", 1988 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Democrats for State Senate, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Preliminary Legislative Highlands, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sample Ballot, 1988 (Flat-file 1)
  - Senator Marchi Fifth Amendment Proposal, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Seuffert, George - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Triangle Fire Memorial, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Maltese Photographs, 1988; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 15th Senate District, Queens Enrollment Books - Republican Party, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bumper Stickers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Big Brothers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Ferraro Campaign Mailer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Maltese, Andy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - New York State Conservative Party, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Presidential Electors Voting Slips, Undated (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
  - Queens Candidate Flyers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Queens Subway Option Study", Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Senate Subject Files, 1965-2009; 22.7 cubic ft.
  - New York's World's Fair, 1965; 1978; 1981; 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aqueduct/Ozone-Howard Little League, 1980; 1992; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Grand Jury Reform, 1984-1985; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Establishment of an Italian Cultural Center at St. John's University, 1986; 1989; 1991-1993; 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A.S.P.C.A and the Pet Food Tax, 1986; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Files, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1988 (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
  - Community Events, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Election Congratulations Letters, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Joseph J. DioGuardi, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Events, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pamphlets, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Senate Office Automation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Senate Election - Serphin Maltese, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Serf Maltese Swearing In, 1989 January 3 (Video-tape 1)
  - Sen. Maltese 15:00, 1989 June 12 (Video-tape 2)
  - Administrative Files, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Bicentennial Presidential Inaugural, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arlene Fiumano, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Carousel Art - Constance Del Vecchio Maltese, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Christ the King, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Community Events, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Drug Hearing, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Energy, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Executive Proclamation, 1989 (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
  - Financial Disclosure System, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Firearms, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Flushing Meadows Corona Park, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Grants, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Greater Ridgewood Restoriation Corp., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Higher Education, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Immigration, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Informed Consent, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Intrepid - Veterans Meeting, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Italian Americans, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Katyn, Poland Memorial, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Legislative Events, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Martin J. Knorr Caregiver's Center Inc., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Photographs, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ridgewood - Seneca Senior Citzens Center, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ronald Lauder Mayoral Campaign, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Senate Session '89 with State Senator Serphin Maltese, 1989 (Video-tape 3)
  - State Senators' Contact Information, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - State of New York Legislative Resolution, 1989 (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
  - Telephone Directory - New York Sate Senate, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - YMCA of Greater New York, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Christ the King and Martin Luther High School, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Editorial Letters, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Foster Grandparents Program, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Irish American Unity Conference, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Public Hearing, Ozone Park: "Queens and Kids Against Drugs.", 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Wyckoff Heights, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Local Newspapers, 1989; 1997-1998; 2006; 2008 (Oversize 1, Folder 9)
  - Death Penalty, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Environmental Conservation, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Hospitals, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Howard Beach Civic Association, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Judiciary, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Public Hearing: New York State Veterans' Needs for the 90's, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Building Code Rules - For Sale Signs, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - DWI Public Hearing, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Education, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Funding, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Elections, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Health Care, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Housing and Community Development (1 of 2), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Housing and Community Development (2 of 2), 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Juniper Elbow Co., 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Act to Amend Chapter 733 of the Laws of 1989 Long Island Secession, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Action Report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Files, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Acceptance of Republican Party Nomination, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bernard Fineson Developmental Center and the Queens Borough Developmental Services Office, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Certificate of Appreciation - Patriotism, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Certificate of Election, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Community Events, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Decamp Campaign Literature, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Domestic Partnerships, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Election Inside Police Precincts, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ethics, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Family Courts, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fernandez, Joseph, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Insurance, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Italian Heritage and Culture Month, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - J.F.K Express, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Judicial Screening Committee, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Juniper Elbow Proposal, 1990 (Oversize 1, Folder 10)
  - Juniper Park Civic Association, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Kumar, Bobby, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Maltese Change to Republican - Conservative Party, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Maltese Re-election Campaign of 1990 - Double Cross by Queens GOP - Betrayal by Queens Chair Lilly A. Bachmann (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Maltese - Republican Acceptances, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Maltese Schedule - Meeting with Secretary Kemp, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - McDonalds Drive - Thru, (F.H. 11375), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - New York Code of Evidence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Pamphlets, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Queens Interagency Council on Aging, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Senate Reports, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - September 11th, 1990 - Serphin Maltese Write-in Primary (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - State of New York Legislative Resolution, 1990 (Oversize 1, Folder 11)
  - Air Pollution and Global Warming, 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Elderly/Senior Citizens, 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hunter's Point Development, 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - New York City Industrial and Commercial Incentive Program (ICIP), 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Wittreich, Carol - Donated Photos, 1990; 1993-1994; 2005 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Celebratory Auction, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Engine Company 294, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Uniformed Firefighters Association, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Aqueduct Racetrack, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Condom Distribution in Public School, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Child Abuse Cases, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Maltese (Constance) Columbus Quin., 1991 February 5 (Video-tape 4)
  - Ridgewood Local Development Corp., 1991 March 5 (Video-tape 5)
  - Howard Beach, 1991 March 19 (Video-tape 6)
  - Woodhaven, 1991 April 9 (Video-tape 7)
  - Kiwanis - Frank D'Orazi, Mick Ennis, Dr. Thomas Ventimiglia, 1991 April 30 (Video-tape 8)
  - Forest Hills TV Taping, 1991 May 21 (Video-tape 9)
  - So. Ozone Park, 1991 May 28 (Video-tape 10)
  - TV Taping Dennis Shea Counsel to Rep. Ldr Robert Pole, 1991 May 25 (Video-tape 11)
  - Administrative Files, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Information, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Cards, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Coalition to Save Engine Company 294, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Columbus Portrait, 1991 (Flat-file 2)
  - Community Events, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Maltese - Change to Republican Party, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Maltese Endorsements - Tom Ognibene for City Council, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Murane, John. One Catholic's View of Public Life, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Pamphlets, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Proposed Homeless Shelters, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Queens County Republican Party By - Laws, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Reports, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Middle Village, 1991 (Video-tape 12)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [1 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 13)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [2 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 14)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [3 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 15)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [4 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 16)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [5 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 17)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [6 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 18)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [7 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 19)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [8 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 20)
  - Senate Digest '91 State Senator Serphin Maltese [9 of 9], 1991 (Video-tape 21)
  - State of New York Legislative Resolution, 1991 (Oversize 1, Folder 12)
  - SUNY Downstate Hospital, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Liberty Conservative Club, Inc., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Thomas V. Ognibene Designating Petitions, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 9th Congressional District, Dennis Shea., 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Secession Press Conf., 1992 February 4 (Video-tape 22)
  - Victims Rights, 1992 March 17 (Video-tape 23)
  - Legislative Report with State Senator Serphin Maltese - 15:00, 1992 June 2 (Video-tape 24)
  - Administrative Files, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Aqueduct Bills, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Black History - New York State, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Election, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce Borough of Queens Membership Card, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Community Events, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Columbus Quincentenary, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - COR; A Foundation for Leadership, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Women's Republican Club of Queens County, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dan Quayle, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Education - Children of the Rainbow, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Empire State Pharmaceutical Society, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Greater Ridgewood Youth Council Day Camp, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Resolution Log, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlets, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Pet Cemetery, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Proclamation - From Senator Serphin Maltese, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Queens Secession Proposal, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Quincentennial Alphabet of Discovery, 1992 (Oversize 1, Folder 13)
  - Reports, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ridgewood/Bushwick Seniors, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Serphin Maltese Endorsements, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - St. Johns University Italian Cultural Center, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Christ the King Students, 1993 March 3 (Video-tape 25)
  - Administrative Files, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Christopher Columbus, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Community Development Agency, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Community Events, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Cooperative Housing Reform Legislation, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correction on Canvas; An Exhibition of Inmate Art, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Council Watch, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Environmental Protection, NYC, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Forensic DNA Testing, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Judge James Left Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local School Board Elections, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - New York City Housing Authority, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - New York City Water Board - Public Information Meeting Regarding Water and Sewer Rates, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Oath of Office, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Hill SRM Swearing-in-Ceremony, 1993 (Video-tape 26)
  - Safety Tips Coloring Book, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Senate Research Service - Medical Parole, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - The American Legion Department of New York, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Vincent J. Colasacco Obituary, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Faso for State Comptroller, 1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, 1993; 1995 (Oversize 1, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education of the City of New York, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Borzellieri, Frank, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Citizens Union Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Evan A. Galbraith, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pat Barrett, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - The 1994 Legislative Correspondents Association Show (Oversize 1, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Files, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - American Forest and Paper Association, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Anne Paolucci, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Community Events, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Conservative Opposition to Pataki, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correction on Canvas Calendar, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Department for the Aging, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Eastbound Belt Parkway Ramp, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Family Defense Council, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Federzione Italo - Americana Di Brooklyn and Queens Inc., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Jamaica Water Supply Company, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Legislative Correspondence Association Journal, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Legislative Report, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Official Ballot for the General Election - City of New York, County of Queens, 1994 (Oversize 1, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlets, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Republican State Committee, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rudy Giuliani - Dupe University Pamphlet, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Serphin Maltese Election, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - State Legislative Budget Presentation, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - State of New York Division of Parole Report on Medical Parole, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - State of New York Legislative Resolution, 1994 (Oversize 1, Folder 17)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Wrongful Death, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - George Pataki, 1994; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Letters from Serphin Maltese with Photos, 1994; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Animal Welfare, 1994; 1996-1998; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - All Faiths Cemetery, 1994; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Ringling Brothers and Bamum and Bailey Correspondence, 1994; 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Files, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Christ The King, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Community Events (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Community Events (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Community School Board 24 Public Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Community School Board - District 27 Budget Summaries and News, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - District Attorney of Kings Country - Assault Law Reform, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Inauguration of Governor George Pataki, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Italian American Political Affairs, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - National Republican Congressional Committee, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New York State Bar Association - Death Penalty, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Queens County Republican Party Chairman Joseph DeFronzo, 1995; Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Reports (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Reports (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Republican Party Designation Petition, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Rules for New York State Independence Party Platform, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Smithsonian Enola Gay Exhibit, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - State and Local Coalition on Immigration, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Queens County Republican Campaign - Board of Elections, 1995; Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - American Conservative Union, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Public School 88, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Juniper Valley Park Roller Hockey Rink, 1995; 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - City Parks Foundation - Pulls Farm Cemetery, 1995-1998; Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Buena Vida Nursing Home, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire Senate Resolutions, 1995-2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Files (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Files (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Community Events, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (1 of 11), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (2 of 11), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (3 of 11), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (4 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (5 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (6 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (7 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (8 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (9 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (10 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (11 of 11), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cyber Sex Legislation, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dole - Kemp Campaign Sticker, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Flight '96 Airshow, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hon. Anthony Seminerio, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - John Seminerio - Democratic District Leader Campaign, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Proclamation, 1996 (Oversize 1, Folder 18)
  - M. A. D. D., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New York State Supreme Court Respondent's Brief, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlets, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Public School 87, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Reports, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Safety Tips Coloring Book, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - "Walking Distance - A Step by Step Guide Through Belmont", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Public School 101, 1996; Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - I.S. 146 School, 1996; 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Airport Rail Link, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "Festa Italiana" Posters, 1996-1997 (Oversize 1, Folder 19)
  - Intermediate School 77, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - New York City Department for the Aging, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)